Finding Aid for the USA for Africa Records LSC.1669
UCLA Library Special Collections
USA for Africa records
1986-1989
UCLA Library Special Collections
Buchanan, Christopher
LSC.1669
112.5 Linear Feet (213 boxes, 2 cartons, 4 oversize boxes)
USA for Africa was part of a plan to distribute the proceeds of a musical recording to benefit famine victims in Africa and projects in the U.S. The collection consists of office files and videotapes related to the activities of USA for Africa.
Conditions Governing Access
Portions of collection unprocessed. Audio and audiovisual materials are unavailable for access. Please see LSC's Access to Unprocessed Collections Policy for more information about levels of discovery and access of special collections materials and registering interest in unprocessed collections.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
CONTAINS UNPROCESSED AUDIO AND AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS: Audio and audiovisual materials are not currently available for access and will require further processing and assessment. If you have questions about this material please email spec-coll@library.ucla.edu.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Christopher Buchanan, 1991.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 9934671153606533
Biographical / Historical
USA for Africa, incorporated under the leadership of Ken Kragen on January 10, 1985, was part of a plan to distribute the proceeds of a musical recording to benefit famine victims in Africa. Forty-five musicians recorded the single titled, "We are the world," on January 28, 1985, which became the quickest selling record in music history. Over $53.1 million was distributed or allocated to projects in Africa and the U.S.
Scope and Contents
Collection consists of office files and videotapes related to the activities of USA for Africa.
Arrangement
This collection has been arranged in the following series: 1. Administrative Files; 2. Administrative Files (Series II); 3. Africa Development Bank; 4. Africa Program Files and Resource Materials; 5. Development Education; 6. Development Education (Rejects); 7. Development Resources; 8. Ethiopia and Others (Rejections); 9. General Resources; 10. Medical Task Force - Rejects and Resource Material; 11. Miscellaneous Rejections; 12. Miscellaneous Resource Material; 13. Photos / Photo Albums; 14. Proposals / Communications / Information on Organizations; 15. Proposals Accepted and Funded; 16. RD II Rejected Proposals; 17. United Nations Correspondence / Memos; 18. WATW Africa Tapes; 19. W.I.D. Rejects
Musicians--United States--Archival resources.; Nonprofit organizations--United States--Archival resources.; Videotapes.; Business records.; Buchanan, Christopher
- Administrative Files
  - Advertisements for U.S.A. for Africa. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Ambassador Letters. (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Adventist Development and Relief Agency (ADRA) - Adventist Development & Relief Agency International. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - OSA Sonny Adun. (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Africa Faith-Justice Network. (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - African Non-governmental organizations Conference - Dakar, Senegal. (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Agri-Energy Youthtable, Incorporated. (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - A.I.D. (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Aid for Africa. (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Dick America/SBA. (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - American Express Company - Stephen Halsey. (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - AT&T. (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Africa Grants Division Budget Correspondence. (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Africa Grants Department - Memos/Correspondence. (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Africa Reports (Box 1, Folder 15-17)
    - Africa Drought Study. (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Report on Mozambique by Maurice Strong. (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - U.S.A. for Africa Report from Ron Elliott. (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Africa/Program Review Board Material. (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Program Review Board (Box 1, Box 2)
    - [No further description available]. (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Meetings. (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - U.S.A. for Africa. (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Band/Aid Meeting w/Irwin Redlener., November 17, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Band-Aid/Live-Aid. (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Bankprint. (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Better World Society. (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Biomass Users Network. (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Boys Club. (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Breakthrough Foundation. (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Breskin, David. (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Bristol Meyers. (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - John Bryant, House of Representatives. (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Burnes, Karen. (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - C.A.R.E. (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - California Cattle Services. (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - California Public-Private Partnership Commission. (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Cartier. (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Cartoons. (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Cartoon - Thanksgiving strips. (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - CBS Records. (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - CBS Special - "A Year of Giving." (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - CBS Television. (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Harry Chapin. (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Central American Refugee Center. (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - C.O.D.E.L. - Coordination in Development. (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Compact for African Development. (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Concert for Africa. (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Consulting (between here & Africa). (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Development & Proposals (Box 2, Box 3)
    - American Associates - Ben Gurion University of the Negev. (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Wildlife Preservation Agency. (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Unfoldered material. (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Edge of Survival. (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Blake Edwards Entertainment. (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Events. (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Ford Foundation. (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Friends of Africa in America. (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Senator John Garamendi. (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Government Communications. (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Glen, John. (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Global Energy Society. (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Global Parliamentarians for Population and Development. (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Stanley Gortikov. (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Griffen Television. (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Ben Gurion University. (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Tony Hall. (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Hawaii for Africa - Debbie Gottheil. (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Hear N Aid. (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Howell Hurst. (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Hunger Project. (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - International Institute for Environment Development. (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Unfoldered material. (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Interaction Correspondence., 1986 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Interaction. (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Interaction Correspondence., 1987 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - International Development Conference. (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - International Fund for Agricultural Development. (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - I.C.S.E.P. (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - I.F.D.C. (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - International Institute for Environment Development (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Japan - Television Show. (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Jazz for Life. (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Jazz to End Hunger. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Unfoldered material. (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Timmie Jensen, U.S. House of Representatives. (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Journalists for Africa. (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - JEF Judin/Profits for Peace. (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Martin Luther King Jr. Center. (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Kragen Awards/United Nations. (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Los Angeles Street scene. (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Labor Institute of Public Affairs. (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Ladimir Enterprises, Incorporated. (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Lawyer's Committee for Civil Rights Under Law. (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Africa - 3 part series for Public Television - David Lamb. (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - National University of Lesotho. (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Robert W. Linville/International. (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Change the World - Stuart Levin. (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Labor Institute of Public Affairs. (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Martin Luther King, Jr. Center. (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence - Medical Task Force., 1986 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Medical Task Force - Memorandums., 1986 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Medical Task Force - Press Releases. (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Unfoldered material. (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Ralph Nader. (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - National Student Campaign vs. Hunger - Joel Ario. (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Unfoldered material. (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - National Student Campaign vs. Hunger. (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - New Music seminar. (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Unfoldered material. (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - New Renaissance Center. (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - O.A.U. (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Unfoldered material. (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - O.E.O.A. (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Opportunities Industrialization Centers International. (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Operation California. (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - OTA - Office of Technology Assessment. (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Overseas Development Council. (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Organization of African States. (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Oxfam/U.S. (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - The Panama Foundation. (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Parents of Watts. (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Park West Children's Fund. (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Peace Corps. (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Peace Foundation. (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - People to People. (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Population Crisis Committee. (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Press release. (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Radio Events. (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Read a Vision. (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Round Table - Bill Spagnolo. (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Marty Rogol - U.S.A. for Africa, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 14-15)
    - Memorandums. (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence. (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - U.S.A. for Africa Correspondence, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 1-2)
    - January-May 1986. (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Requests for Funding Responses. (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Board of Directors - Approvals. (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Unfoldered material. (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Harriet Sternberg. (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Maurice Strong (Box 9, Folder 6-7)
    - Correspondence. (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - B.A.C.A. weekend. (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Stamps. (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Speaking invitations. (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Sidel, Vic (Hunger Watch). (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Dick Smith/Brock Peters. (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - SEEDS (Box 9, Folder 12-13)
    - Christians Concerned About Hunger. (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Patents. (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Save the Children. (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Say Thanks America. (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Thornhill, Andrew. (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Supervision Services, International. (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Technology Development Corporation. (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Til-Wagner, Benito - Business tie-ins. (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Unfoldered material. (Box 10, Folder 4, 8)
  - Unitarian Universalist Service Committee. (Box 10, Folder 5, 11)
  - United Nations (Box 10)
    - Development Fund for Women. (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous. (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - General Assembly - Special Session on Africa. (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Association of the United States of America. (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - International Fund for Agricultural Development (IFAD). (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - UN and U.S. Private Sector African Famine Response., 1984-1986 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - World Food Council. (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - U.N.I.C.E.F. (Box 10, Box 11)
      - [No further description available]. (Box 10, Folder 13)
      - John Richardson. (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Winterland. (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - The World Bank. (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - "We Are The World" Television Special. (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Warner Brothers (Box 11, Folder 5-6)
    - Publishers contracts. (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Requests to use song. (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - World Food Council. (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Unlabeled folder. (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - World Health Day [empty]. (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - World Food Day. (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - World Hunger Year. (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Unfoldered material. (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Unlabeled folder. (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - World Hunger Media Awards., 1986 (Box 12, Folder 3-5)
    - [No further description available]. (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Entries. (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Invitations lists. (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Unfoldered material. (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Radio finalists - WHMA., 1986; (Cassette tapes) (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - M.H.R. Correspondence. (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - U.S.A. for Africa Correspondence., May-September 1986 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Unfoldered material. (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - World Vision - Drug list. (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - World Showvision Network, Incorporated. (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Administrative Files - Series II
  - Untitled binder - part 1. (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - City of Los Angeles - U.S.A. for Africa Proclamation. (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Hawaii for Africa. (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Influence Directory. (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Inside Story. (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Fast Food Program. (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - International Forum on Technology. (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Jazz Aid. (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Jazz to End Hunger. (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - KUVO 89.3 FM (Denver). (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - House of Representatives. (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - International News clippings. (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Fundraisers. (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Untitled binder - part 2. (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Legal. (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Fedeke Gemechu. (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Dr. Rose Gibbs/Charles Drew Medical. (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Greater New Bedford for Africa, Incorporated. (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Legal. (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - M.B.I. Productions - Mary Ellen Bickford. (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - The Living Wall Garden. (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Los Angeles Human Relations Commission. (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Los Angeles Street scene., (September 28/29, 1985) (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Management Applied Programming, Incorporated. (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous articles. (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Parents International. (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Parents International - Ethiopia. (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Office of the Lieutenant Governor, Hawaii. (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Unfoldered material. (Box 16, Folder 1-3)
  - DIC Enterprises, Incorporated ("We Are The World" animation). (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Rambo. (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Read-Aid (Phil Harnage). (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Rhythms of the Village (African Dance & Theatre Company). (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Read-A-Vision. (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - U.S.A. For Africa news articles. (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - U.S.A. For Africa logo. (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - United Nations. (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Senate of South Carolina. (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Sports Aid. (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Africa Development Bank
  - Africa and the African Development Bank - Report of Committee of Ten. (Box 165, Folder 1)
  - African Development Bank Group - Abuja - Nigeria., May 26-27, 1989 (Box 165, Folder 2)
  - Senior Level Debt Conversion Workshop. (Box 165, Folder 3)
  - African Development Bank (Box 165, Box 166)
    - Pay statements to "Republic of Gambia." (Box 165, Folder 4)
    - Appraisal report for water control & rural development in Upper Volta. (Box 165, Folder 5)
    - Appraisal report for COMOE integrated rural development in Upper Volta. (Box 165, Folder 6)
    - Appraisal report for Jahaly - Pacharr smallholder rice project (Gambia). (Box 165, Folder 7)
    - Appraisal report on Selingue rural development project (Mali). (Box 165, Folder 8)
    - Appraisal report for livestock project in Soum province (Burkina Faso). (Box 166, Folder 1)
    - Appraisal report for irrigation agricultural development project in Anambe basin (Senegal). (Box 166, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous papers. (Box 166, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence. (Box 166, Folder 4)
- Africa Program Files & Resource Materials
  - Overseas Education Fund (OEF) - Correspondence. (Box 181, Folder 4)
  - Kulima (Box 182, Folder 1-2)
    - Project summary - 06R01. (Box 182, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence - 06R01. (Box 182, Folder 2)
  - French Association of Volunteers of Progress (Box 182, Folder 3-5)
    - Financial information - 07701. (Box 182, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence - 07701. (Box 182, Folder 4)
    - Project summary - 07701. (Box 182, Folder 5)
  - A.C.O.R.D. (Box 182, Folder 6-9)
    - Project summary - 09R01. (Box 182, Folder 6)
    - Progress report - 09R01. (Box 182, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence - 09R01. (Box 182, Folder 8)
    - Financial information - 09R01. (Box 182, Folder 9)
  - A.B.A.C.E.D. (Box 182, Folder 10-13)
    - Financial information - 08712. (Box 182, Folder 10)
    - Project summary - 08712. (Box 182, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence - 08712. (Box 182, Folder 13)
  - Emmanuel Baptist Church (Box 182, Folder 14-17)
    - Progress report - 03704. (Box 182, Folder 14)
    - Financial information - 03704. (Box 182, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence - 03704. (Box 182, Folder 16)
    - Project summary - 03704. (Box 182, Folder 17)
  - Mozambique Red Cross - 06710. (Box 182, Folder 18)
  - Association Prom. Fem. le Sport (Box 182, Folder 19-21)
    - Financial information - 01702. (Box 182, Folder 19)
    - Project summary - 01702. (Box 182, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence - 01702. (Box 182, Folder 21)
  - Technica - Financial information - 06704. (Box 182, Folder 22)
  - A.V.D. (Box 182, Folder 23-26)
    - Financial information - W.I.D. 01901. (Box 182, Folder 23)
    - Project summary - W.I.D. 01901. (Box 182, Folder 24)
    - Progress report - W.I.D. 01901. (Box 182, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence - W.I.D. 01901. (Box 182, Folder 26)
  - Caritas (Box 182, Folder 27-29)
    - Project summary - 05401. (Box 182, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence - 05401. (Box 182, Folder 28)
    - Financial information - 05401. (Box 182, Folder 29)
  - C.O.P.A.F.O. (Box 182, Box 183)
    - Correspondence - 01705. (Box 182, Folder 30)
    - Project summary - 01705. (Box 183, Folder 1)
    - Financial information - 01705. (Box 183, Folder 2)
  - Kulima - Progress report - 06R01. (Box 183, Folder 3-4)
    - Progress report - 06R01. (Box 183, Folder 3)
    - Financial information - 06R01. (Box 183, Folder 4)
  - Save the Children Fund (SCF) (Box 183, Folder 5-9)
    - Protective health - Correspondence - 04301. (Box 183, Folder 5)
    - Protective health - Procurement - 04301. (Box 183, Folder 6)
    - Protective health - Reports - 04301. (Box 183, Folder 7)
    - Proposal & Grant Application - 04301. (Box 183, Folder 8)
    - Protective health - Budget - 04301. (Box 183, Folder 9)
  - Unfoldered material. (Box 183, Folder 10)
  - African Association for Literacy & Adult Education. (Box 184, Folder 1)
  - Tape log. (Box 184, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous publications. (Box 184, Folder 3)
  - I.R.E.D. (Box 184, Folder 4)
  - Institute of International Education. (Box 184, Folder 5)
  - International Labor Office. (Box 184, Folder 6)
  - Innovative Housing. (Box 184, Folder 7)
  - Africa Leadership Forum. (Box 184, Folder 8)
  - A.W.C. report on standardization of training and production. (Box 185, Folder 1)
  - World Conservation Union. (Box 185, Folder 2)
  - F.D.E.A. (Box 185, Folder 3)
  - Islamic African Relief Agency. (Box 185, Folder 4)
  - Project summary for Sudan - rejected. (Box 185, Folder 5)
  - Association for Women in Development. (Box 185, Folder 6)
  - World Resources Institute. (Box 185, Folder 7)
  - C.R.D.A. (Box 185, Folder 8)
  - Association Malienne pour l'Insertion Professionelle des Jeunes. (Box 185, Folder 9)
  - Association Malienne pour la protection de l'Environment. (Box 185, Folder 10)
  - SAG originals. (Box 209, Folder 26)
- Development Education
  - Museum of World Solutions - HNA07. (Box 122, Folder 1)
  - The Development Group (Box 122, Folder 2-5)
    - Project summary - DE830. (Box 122, Folder 2)
    - DE830. (Box 122, Folder 3)
    - Financial information - DE830. (Box 122, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence - DE830. (Box 122, Folder 5)
  - N.C.N.W. (Box 122, Folder 6-9)
    - Project summary - DE836. (Box 122, Folder 6)
    - Progress report - DE836. (Box 122, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence - DE836. (Box 122, Folder 8)
    - Financial information - DE836. (Box 122, Folder 9)
  - Global Exchange (Box 122, Folder 10-13)
    - Progress report - DE837. (Box 122, Folder 10)
    - Project summary - DE837. (Box 122, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence - DE837. (Box 122, Folder 12)
    - Financial information - DE837. (Box 122, Folder 13)
  - Africa News Service (Box 122, Folder 14-17)
    - Correspondence - DE841. (Box 122, Folder 14)
    - Project summary - DE841. (Box 122, Folder 15)
    - Financial information - DE841. (Box 122, Folder 16)
    - Progress report - DE841. (Box 122, Folder 17)
  - Rodale (Box 122, Folder 18-21)
    - Progress report - DE842. (Box 122, Folder 18)
    - Project summary - DE842. (Box 122, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence - DE842. (Box 122, Folder 20)
    - Financial information - DE842. (Box 122, Folder 21)
  - Children to Children Foundation (Box 122, Folder 22-23)
    - Financial information - DE843. (Box 122, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence - DE843. (Box 122, Folder 23)
  - Africa Fund (Box 122, Folder 24-27)
    - Correspondence - DE851. (Box 122, Folder 24)
    - Progress report - DE851. (Box 122, Folder 25)
    - Project summary - DE851. (Box 122, Folder 26)
    - Financial information - DE851. (Box 122, Folder 27)
  - U.U.S.C. (Box 122, Folder 28-29, 31)
    - Correspondence - DE852. (Box 122, Folder 28)
    - Project summary - DE852. (Box 122, Folder 29)
    - Financial information - DE852. (Box 122, Folder 31)
  - Unitarian - Progress report - DE852. (Box 122, Folder 30)
  - O.C.A. (Box 123, Folder 1-3)
    - Financial information - DE854. (Box 123, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence - DE854. (Box 123, Folder 2)
    - Project summary - DE854. (Box 123, Folder 3)
  - Crossroads - Progress report - DE854. (Box 123, Folder 4)
  - O.D.N. (Box 123, Folder 5-8)
    - Project summary - DE856. (Box 123, Folder 5)
    - Project summary - DE856. (Box 123, Folder 5)
    - Progress report - DE856. (Box 123, Folder 6)
    - Financial information - DE856. (Box 123, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence - DE856. (Box 123, Folder 8)
  - Emang Basadi Women's organization (Box 123, Folder 9-12)
    - Financial information - DE860. (Box 123, Folder 9)
    - Project summary - DE860. (Box 123, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence - DE860. (Box 123, Folder 11)
    - Progress report - DE860 [empty]. (Box 123, Folder 12)
  - Africa Fund (Box 123, Folder 13-16)
    - Project summary - DE861. (Box 123, Folder 13)
    - Financial information - DE861. (Box 123, Folder 14)
    - Progress report - DE861 [empty]. (Box 123, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence - DE861. (Box 123, Folder 16)
  - South Africa Now. (Box 123, Folder 17)
  - Panos (Box 123, Folder 18-21)
    - Project summary - DE862. (Box 123, Folder 18)
    - Progress report - DE862. (Box 123, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence - DE862. (Box 123, Folder 20)
    - Financial information - DE862. (Box 123, Folder 21)
  - World Hunger Year (Box 123, Folder 22-25)
    - Financial information - DE863. (Box 123, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence - DE863. (Box 123, Folder 23)
    - Project summary - DE863 [empty]. (Box 123, Folder 24)
    - Progress Report - DE863 [empty]. (Box 123, Folder 25)
  - Food First (Box 123, Folder 26-29)
    - Project Summary - DE864. (Box 123, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence - DE864. (Box 123, Folder 27)
    - Progress Report - DE864. (Box 123, Folder 28)
    - Financial information - DE864. (Box 123, Folder 29)
  - N.C.I.H. (Box 123, Folder 30-33)
    - Progress Reports - DE865. (Box 123, Folder 30)
    - Project Summary - DE865. (Box 123, Folder 31)
    - Financial information - DE865. (Box 123, Folder 32)
    - Correspondence - DE865. (Box 123, Folder 33)
  - Panos - War Wounds (Box 124, Folder 1-4)
    - Financial information - DE866. (Box 124, Folder 1)
    - Project Summary - DE866. (Box 124, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence - DE866. (Box 124, Folder 3)
    - Progress Report - DE866 [empty]. (Box 124, Folder 4)
  - The Africa Fund (Box 124, Folder 5-8)
    - Project Summary - DE867. (Box 124, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence - DE867. (Box 124, Folder 7)
    - Financial information - DE867. (Box 124, Folder 8)
  - Development. (Box 124, Folder 12)